there are fewer and fewer Russians in Russia
русских в России стаёт всё меньше и
and the population of Russia is declining
меньше и население России сокращается
no Russian man is not blood this is
нет русский человек - это не кровь это
not blood Slavic man is blood Slavs
не кровь Славянский человек это кровь
ruv less and Russians are a
славянс рув меньше а русски это а
Russian - Who is Russian Russianness
русский - Это кто русский русскость
Russianness read our classics there
русскость почитайте там наших классиков
Russianness is no longer blood  Russianness
русскость - это уже не кровь русскость -
is how to say it’s like a
это как сказать так как
religion
религия Здравствуйте
Hello Hello Oh, I see your flag
Здравствуйте О я так вижу у вас флаг
is so
такой вы этот
Orthodox you are Yes of course Oh I see you
православный Да конечно О я вижу у вас
still have a Tsar, you are an admirer of the Tsar
ещё царь вы царе почитатель
so not at all Luda How do you feel about
так не вообще Люде Как вы относитесь к
that? I’m interested in how you feel about the
тому Мне интересно как вы относитесь к
fact that Lenin, these communists
тому что Ленин вот эти коммунисты
overthrew the Tsar,
скинули царя
all sorts of bad things, yes. And why does Russia not have control over
всякие плохо да А почему Россия
Lenin himself, but simply
вле не не Ленина самого а просто труп
his corpse does not allow history to be rewritten? No,
его историю не даёт переписывать Не ну
look, you have Lenin’s corpse lying there  in the
смотрите у вас лежит труп Ленина в
Mausoleum this is
Мавзолее это же
correct Well, this is from the point of view I heard
правильно Ну это с точки зрения Я слышал
that this is from a scientific point of view now now from a scientific
что это с научно сечас сейчас с научной
point of view it is already valuable as if there is already
точки зрения уже ценен как бы уже там
some kind of
какая-то
Kato Gru uny not Dat zani
Като Гру уны не Дат зани
but I understand
пото понимаю
that his wife  his legal wife
что его жена законная его жена законна
was legal was against it, she wanted to
была против она хотела его
bury him, no one was an ambassador,
захоронить никто не послу
all the excursions. So they go.
все экскурсии Так они же идут Как
Like worship, from the point of view of
поклонение вроде с точки зрения
Christianity, worship of the dead, so
христианства поклонение мёртвому вот и
he was the Antichrist, he generally denied
он же антихрист был он вообще отрицал
religion, denied I don’t know, I
религию отрицал Я не знаю
understood it, but what kind of power is it like
это понял а какя власть она как
pagan?  it was like a new pagan
языческая такая была как новая языческая
Faith, some kind of such Uh-huh I understand, it’s just that
Вера какая-то такая Угу Понял просто
somehow it turns out that in Russia now it’s
как-то получается в России сейчас
combined and this Soviet power and the
совмещается и вот эта Советская власть и
imperial one In short, everything is so mixed up in  a bunch of
имперская Короче всё так намеша в кучу
Stalin, too, so many
Сталин тоже столько столько
Orthodox SPO
православных СПО
priests, these are the years of repression to the
священников это ри годы репрессии до
sacred cool, they don’t give it, don’t
священ прикольном не дают это не
forget, I think that generation which, in
забываем думаю то поколение которое в
principle, is for him. This is history, I think
принципе для него Это история думаю
when that generation
когда поколение то
will probably leave and Lenin will be removed. I
уйдёт наверное и Ленина уберут Мне
think how do you feel about Putin, don’t
кажется а как вы относитесь к Путину не
create unnecessary  just these ones, I
наводить лишних вот этих просто вот я
see that Putin is for Lenin, for Stalin. How do
смотрю что Путин Он за Ленина за Сталина
you feel about him?
Как вы к нему
No, he’s not for Lenin, not for
относитесь Да нет он не за Ленина не за
Stalin, he’s just loyal to
Сталина он просто лоялен ко
everything. Well  let's say Putin is for the Tsar or
всему Ну давайте так Путин за царя или
for Lenin, the President is the President of everyone, yes
за Ленина президент президент всех да Ну
Well, Putin, as he says, that Lenin was
вот Путин Как говорит что Ленин был
a villain, that yes, that they killed the Tsar, made
злодеем что да что убили царя сделали
a revolution,
революцию
he is a
дарственный он
statesman, How can he
деятель Как он может
listen to the people? I say,
быть прислушивается к народу Я же говорю
those who honor and respect are still alive.
ещ живы ещё живы те которые почитают и
Leninsky
ленински
[music]
[музыка]
how I think this generation will go, I
как я думаю уйдёт это
understand, it just turns out
поколение так понял просто получается
somehow wild for me, but I see he
для меня как-то дико но я смотрю он он
takes it and before he seemed to be there for
берёт и раньше он там вроде как был за
tsar Putin everything And then Lenin
царя Путин всё А тут начинает вот Ленин
Stalin begins, it turns out he is resurrecting
Сталин это же получается он воскрешает
these
вот эти
uh Soviet ideas,
э советские идеи
atheists, he has democratic ideas.
безбожники у него демократические идеи
Let’s say in America. By the way, I
Вот вы допустим вот в Америке Я кстати в
saw it in America, I don’t remember in which state
Америке видел там не помню в каком штате
on May 9 they were wearing Soviet old
на 9 мая одеты в советские эти старые
uniforms  and there people walk around with these Glory to the
формы и там люди ходят с этими Слава
CPSU Well, it’s just that I, I, I see that for
КПСС Ну просто просто я я я смотрю что
example, a Democratic country Yes, in
например Демократическая страна Да в
Russia Lenin Stalin is revered there,
России там почитается Ленин Сталин вот
these are the communists who fought with the Faith.
эти коммунисты которые боролись с Верой
And for example, Denikin and Kolchak Why  they were
А например деникин да Колчак Почему их
not reburied near the Kremlin
не не перезахоронили возле кремлёвской
wall, for example,
стены например
now, under the current government, it is
это сейчас при нынешнем правлении
necessary to return them to their historical land
надо вернуть их на историческую землю
to show that we are honoring
показать что мы чти сечас
now, the authorities are not
часне власти никого не
burying anyone, I understand. How do you think
хоронят понял А как Как вы считаете
now, for example, Putin is pursuing a policy to
сейчас например Путин ведёт политику на
increase the Russian people or to
приумножение российского народа или на
reduce the knife increase A  how, for
уменьшение ноже приумножение А как
example, did Russians increase in
например русские приумножить например в
number over the last 10 and 20 years of
числе за последние там 10 и за 20 лет
his reign? I saw statistics that
его правления Я видел статистику что
Russians are dying out. But for example, not  Russians
русские вымирают А например не русские
breed
размножаются
there And who do you mean Russian mu
там А кого вы имеете в виду русскую му
Well, look For example, if we look Yes
Ну смотрите Например если мы смотрим Да
in Russian in Russians for a minute for a
в рус в русских на минуточку на
minute for a minute for a minute I have a grandfather in armor, be
минуточку на минуточку у меня дед латы
careful what that you have a
поосторожнее что что у вас
grandfather I have a Latvian as a watchman, well, no, I’m
дед у меня Латыш по сторож ну не ну я
correct, I’m looking  Right now the Russians Yes,
правильно я смотрю Вот сейчас русские Да
for example, the Russians are dying out if you want
например русские вымирают если крови вы
blood if you want blood Well
крови если если вы крови хотите Ну на
look at no Now you mean
нет смотрите Сейчас вы имеете в виду
Russia for Russians No no I’m saying that
Россия для русских Нет нет я говорю что
there are fewer and fewer Russians in Russia
русских в России стаёт всё меньше и
and the population of Russia is declining
меньше и население России сокращается
no Russian people - this is not blood this is
нет русский человек - это не кровь это
not blood Slavic people are blood the
не кровь Славянский человек это кровь
Slavs understood
славянс понял
Russian and Russian is who A Russian - This is
русский а русский это кто А руский - Это
who uh Russian Russianness Russianness
кто э русский русскость русскость
read our classics there Russianness is
почитайте там наших классиков русскость
no longer blood Russianness - that's how to
- это уже не кровь русскость - это э как
say  since the religion has already
сказать так как религия та такая уже
turned out like this. That is, it turns out
получилась То есть получается
Russian, here in 800 in 812 in 812 we
русский вот у нас в 800 в 812 году в 812
heard there was such a general, uh
году слышали был такой генерал ээ
Bagration
Багратион
uh Bagration  Do you hear Bagration or not
ээ Багратион Багратиона слышишь или нет
what I called you Bagration? Yes, you
то что я же вам назвал Багратион Да
heard Bagration, you know who you know
слышали Багратион он знаете кто знаете
who he is by nationality, I don’t know,
кто он по национальности не знаю
probably
наверное
Tatar, you don’t know, but now I’m
татарин не знаете вот Я вот сейчас
a little
немножко
enlightened Yes, Russian is the
просвещённый Да русский - это тот
person who Yes, this is the person
человек который Да это тот человек
who does not allow trampling uh  of
который не даёт топтать ээ
their ancestors the achievements of their ancestors
своих предков достижений своих предков
Well, that is, it turns out For example, Ramzan
Ну то есть получается Например Рамзан
Kadyrov, he is also Russian, his faith is a pack of
Кадыров он тоже руский свою веру свора
Ramza, look Ramzan Kadyrov does not allow
рамза смотри Рамзан Кадыров не даёт
his faith to be trampled on  he is
топтать свою веру он
Russian, he doesn’t give, he doesn’t give Yes, Ramzan
русский не даёт не даёт Да Рамзан
Kadyrov is Russian, Ramzan Kadyrov is even more
Кадыров русский Рамзан Кадыров ещё более
Russian, I understand correctly, that is, I
русский понял то есть я правильно
understand correctly that, for example, It’s not
понимаю что например Это не
nationality, it’s blood, I understand, that is, I
национальность это кровь понял то есть я
understand correctly, I understand that, for example, a
понимаю правильно понимаю что например
million people from Indonesia can come and
могут приехать миллион людей из
settle in Russia and they
Индонезии Да поселиться в России и они
will become  Russians
станут русскими
Yes, I
Да
understood this mentality, so let’s say
понял это менталитет так скажем
mentally, the mentality Yeah, but this
ментально менталитет Ага по уже это уже
is already Russian now, here are the Slavs Yes,
это русский сейчас вот славян Да
Slavic blood is Slavic blood,
славянская кровь - это славянская кровь
this is with this and what and what  the mentality
это с вот а в чём а в чём менталитет
of the Russian, for example, how can you determine by the
русского например как вот определить по
mentality
менталитету
of the Russian, well, the Russians are held together by the
русского ну э русских скрепляет
Orthodox faith thousands of years
православная вера когда-то Тысячи лет
ago, and this is what
назад скрепил И вот это вот это ий
holds them
держится
together, which many want to destroy.
такая скрепа которую хотят разрушить
Well, you said that
многие Ну вы же сказали что Кадыров
Kadyrov is Russian. Kadyrov is a Muslim, he has
русский Кадыров мусульманин он
nothing to do with the Orthodox Scrapi.  Well,
православной Скрепи ничего не имеет Ну а
you read this, you are right to glorify
вы читали вы вы вы правильно славить
God, they are right to glorify God, they are
Бога они правильно славят Бога они
Allah, you
Аллаха вы
read
читали
this, then all Muslims are also Russian,
этот то все мусульмане тоже русские
it turns out Regardless Where  they live in Sudan,
получается Независимо Где живут в судане
for example, there in Morocco they are all Russians
например там в Марокко это всё русские
I say Russian people Russian people
Я говорю русский народ русский народ
Scrapi once upon a time Orthodoxy and Russian
Скрепи когда-то православие и русский
people do not divide people of nationality into
человек не делит людей национальности на
religions this is dirt Nehru I understand they are
вероисповедания это дерт Неру Поня такие
like our very last Nehru was
как вот у нас самый последний Неру был
very famous this gi and his minions
очень известный это ги и его приспешники
they divided there by blood by skulls they
они Дели там по крови по черепам там
sorted out the Russian
разбирались русский
people, so Christ’s disciples asked him
народ вот у Христа спросили его ученики
once they asked, let’s find out our brothers, he
как-то спросили узнаем братьев наших он
didn’t say there, believe there, that to whom they can
не сказал там повере там что кому они мо
do business  you will recognize them by their deeds. Understand your
по делам их узнаете по делам Поня дела
brother’s deeds, everything, that is, it turns out, I understand everything, it
брата всё то есть получается все понял
turns out, look, I
то получается смотрите я правильно
understand correctly that Kadyrov is
понимаю что Кадыров
Russian. Well, you need to ask him, does
русский Ну надо у него спросить считает
he think so? No, what do you think? Well, is he
он се Не ну вы как считаете Ну он
Russian or not Russian, but he is based on his deeds. So
русский или не русский он ж по делам Вот
you judge him, he  Russian I I I can’t tell
вы его судите он русский я я я не могу
him I can’t tell him his
ему Я не могу ему определить его его
inner state Well, you
внутреннее состояние Ну вы Гитлера
determined Hitler that he was Nehru,
определили что он Неру а
but Kadyrov Is he Russian or not
вот Кадыров Он русский или не
Russian? I determined Hitler that they
русский Я Гитлера определил что он
said that Hitler had his affairs, he had his
сказали что Гитлер был у него дела у
affairs Karo
него дела
himself  Kadyrov’s story to himself is
Каро он сам себе сказа Кадыров же
correct. So Kadyrov also fought
правильно Так Кадыров тоже типа воевал
against the Russians. Kadyrov fought against the
против русских Кадыров воевал против
Russians in the first and second. Kadyrov doesn’t
русских в первой и второй Кадыров не
divide people
делит людей
into why he says Chechens, yes he says
на почему он говорит чеченцы да говорит
because we are Muslims, he says he
потому что мы мусульмане он говорит
divides
делит
you are Orthodox, they are Muslims,
вы православные они мусульмане
he fought against the Orthodox. Well,
делит он воевал против православных Ну
yes in  the first Chechen in the second type they
да в первое чеченской во второй типа они
fought, his dad
воевали батя его
fought And
воевал А
look, this is against the politics of this
смотрите это проти политики вот
all the Amori heads of the main ruler of Russia
этой всё амори глав главный ровин России
he also
он тоже русский
turns out to be Russian, well, he has to with Well, who is
получается ну надо у него с Ну подо кто
Russian
рус
with You Burn Wed I am an example for you, I
с Вы же Горите сре я вам пример я вам
gave you an example, you can read this Can you
пример это дал можете почитать А можете
give me examples of Russians Well, name examples of
мне примеры русских Ну назовите примеры
Russians,
русских
I can name examples that are not Russian,
э я я могу примеры назвать не русских не
but I don’t have Russians  I myself can
А мне русских не русских я сам могу
name a bunch of Russians, Russian people are not Russian
назвать куча русские люди не русские
people who betray their ancestors, sharpen
люди которые предают своих предков точат
their faith, these are not Russian people, that
свою веру это не русские люди то так то
is, Kadyrov is not Russian, if he is a Slav,
есть Кадыров не руский ели он славянин
then look, Kadyrov is not  Russian he
да то смотри Кадыров не русский он
betrayed his ancestors his faith Kadyrov
предал своих предков свою веру Кадыров
betrayed his did not betray his ancestors
предал свои не предал своих предков
betrayed his ancestors the Chechens Yes and
предал своих предков чеченцев Да и
now he works for the Russian for Putin Well
работает сейчас на русского на Путина Ну
Putin is not Russian and how did he betray
Путин же не русский да как он предал
his ancestors betrayed his ancestors yes
своих предков предал своих предков да
Russia his ancestors are the streets of the Russians and he is like
Россия его предки ули россиян а он типа
now  for
сейчас за
them And look, you can name examples of
них А смотрите то можете назвать примеры
Russian examples of non-Russians What are
русского примеры нерусских Какие предки
his ancestors What are his ancestors Akhmat Kadyrov
его Какие предки его его Ахмат Кадыров
generally called for the more Russians
вообще призывал вать чем больше Русских
as many  see how he betrayed his faith
столько сколько смо как он предал веру
and he betrayed Russia, look, let’s say
а а Россию он предал смотрите давайте
that Dzhakhar Dudayev was a traitor to Russia
так джахар Дудаев был предателем России
for
для
you Khar Dudayev
вас хар Дудаев
Yes, a traitor to Russia Yes, I don’t know, he’s
Да предателем России Да не знаю он
probably a traitor to his people, so I
предателем наверно своего народа так В
mean, on the contrary, he’s a hero of his people, he’s
смысле он наоборот герой своего Наро он
a hero of his people, he’s against the occupiers
герой своего народа он против оккупантов
Russia The people the people said that he is not a
Россия Народ народ сказал что он не
hero Cool yes But can you still
герой Прикольно да А можете вс-таки
name an example of a Russian I am with the Chechens I
назвать пример русского я с чеченцами я
work with the Chechens They said that
это с чеченцами работаю Они сказали что
Oh super super yes well  can you give examples of
О супер супер да ну можете примеры
Russian for example Pushkin is
русского например Пушкин
Russian Yes I understand why he is Russian although
русский Да понял а чем он русский хотя
you know who he is who he is by blood so he is
вы знаете кто он кто он по крови так он
by blood Yes he is not Russian and not Russian in Spirit
по крови Да не русский и по Духу не
he wouldn’t be Pushkin’s work
русский он же не бы Пушкина произведение
But he that Pushkin was for his faith you can’t
А он что Пушкин был за веру не можете
say Pushkin  I was there for my faith, I went to
сказать Пушкин был за веру там ходил в
church, don’t say no, do
цер не бубни не буни какая вера была у
n’t say what kind of faith did Pushkin have what faith did Pushkin have
Пушкина какая вера у Пушкина Была ээ
don’t read I’m
не читаю книжки я пишу их не читае я
writing
пишу
[music]
[музыка]
books Come on, you’ve tired me out a lot
книги Да ладно ты меня сильно утомил
Read books, better yet Read them and then
Почитай книжки лучше пу Почитай а потом
we’ll see each other again The last book
мы ещё увидимся последнюю книжку какую я
I wrote, it’s called
которую я написал это называется
intellectual disorders of Russians
э интеллектуальные расстройства Россиян
on religious grounds I know what it’s
на религиозной почве Я знаю как она
called there, nothing smart about you there
называется там ниче умного тебя там
written That you can still
написа Что можете всё-таки пример
give an example of a Russian, just look I don’t
русского привести просто смотрите Я не
read
читаю
books Just tell me an example of at least one
книжки Скажите просто пример хоть одного
Russian Here is a modern one who is a
русского Вот современного кто
modern Russian Prigozhin is a
современный русский Пригожин
Russian Russian so I understand who else  Chubais
русский русский так понял кто ещё Чубайс
Russian really old horse ru Ponya
русский правда старая коне ру Поня
Chubais
Чубайс
Russian no Chubais no understood the shooters
русский нет Чубайс нет понял стрелков
Russian
русский
I say who who did not betray their faith
Я говорю кто кто не предал свою веру
shooters Russian Girkin shooters Is he
стрелков русский гиркин стрелков Он
Russian or
русский или
not he’s just
нет просто он
Russian he betrayed his Fatherland And how he
русский он предал сво Отечество А как он
betrayed his
предал своё
Fatherland is funny I’m just thinking with
Отечество прикольно Просто я думаю при
Russian  ru
русский ру
[music]
[музыка]
life's path and step
жизненный путь а шагу
Russian of course Russian I got it super
русский конечно русский Понял супер А
How did it happen that in the
как так получилось что в государстве
Russian state there are such  great Russian people like
России таких великих русских людей как
Prigozhin are shot down on an airplane, yes And
Пригожин сбивают в самолёте да А таких
great Russian people like shooters are put
великих русских людей как стрелков садят
in
в
prison. Why did you decide that he was shot down?
тюрьму А чего ты решил что его сбили Я
I just don’t know, maybe they didn’t shoot
просто с я не знаю может не сбили может
him down, maybe he himself. Maybe his bomb exploded in the toilet,
сам Может у него взорвался там в туалете
but that’s the question Jesus  was Russian not
бом а е вот вопрос Иисус был русский не
SS Everyone says differently Ponya Yes, but
СШ Все по-разному говорят Поня Да а
Jesus was Russian, so what do you
Иисус был русским вот Как вы
think then Russia didn’t exist so not
считаете тогда ещё России не было так не
Russia Russians were there when the Russians
Россия русские же были когда русские
appeared
появились
Iru he’s not Russian so
Иру он не русский так
but who Okay  Honor at least not but esri
а кто Ладно Почитай хотя бы не а ес сри
if Jesus is not Russian, then who is
если Иисус не русский то кто
he? Yes, just if Jesus is not
он вот просто Да просто если Иисус не
Russian, then who is O he was born in Judea Who is
русский то кто О он родился в иудее Кто
he in Judea Jews are born then he is a Jew
он в Иудеи евреи рождаются то он еврей
So
Так
why don’t I tell you a secret Just
даре я тебе по секрету скажу Только
don’t tell anyone Got it  I understand, that is, I
никому не говори Понял понял то есть я
understand correctly Yes, what happens is that your
правильно понимаю Да что получается вы
hands are burnt, yes, that is, look, you’re
руки подгорел да то есть смотри ты э
Russian, Russian, yes, and what do you
русский русский да а а что у тебя Бог не
mean, God is not Russian? Well, well, you see, God has no
получается Ну Ну понимаешь у Бога нет
nationality, he  so you said
национальности он надо так вы сказали
that he is a Jew, you said that he is a Jew
что он иудей вы вы сказали что он иудей
nationally, you said that Jesus is a Jew
национально вы сказали что Иисус иудей
by birth
по рождению
Yes, he is not Russian by birth either,
Да по рождению тоже не русский го то
look, Jesus is not Russian I am not
смотри то Иисус он не русский Я по
Russian by birth No, he is not Russian
рождени не русский Нет он не русский-то
And when did the Russians appear  Miyu I'll tell my
А когда русские появились мию скажу моей
mom in
мамы во
f Listen here I'm Russian I'm
ф Слушай сюда я руский я
ru you know how my mom is Let's say
ру знаешь как у моей мамы Давай скажи
feel better Let's say
полегчает Давай сказать
Dammers super well done well done yes Okay
даммерс супер молодец молодец да Хорошо
and when  Russians appeared then, if
а когда появились русские тогда вот если
when Jesus was there, there were no Russians when the
когда был Иисус русских не было когда
Russians appeared Read the books, please Dava, I’m
русские Почитай книж пожалуста Дава
just
просто
wondering, Queen Katerina was like
интересно царица Катерина типа была
Russian,
русская
and no matter how much you don’t cringe, look,
а сколько ты не сжа не съезжая смотри
Queen Katerina was
царица Катерина была
Russian, Queen Katerina was
русская царица Катерина была
Russian, Well, you can’t because I’m
русская Ну не можешь потому что я тебе
asking you questions  who knock you out and you
даю вопросы которые тебя выбивают и ты
immediately sit down on the
сразу оп садишься на стержень
inner core, look, Tsarina
внутренний смотри царица
Katerina, Tsarina Katerina, tell her Who
Катерина царица Катерина Скажи она Кто
was on  her nationality was
была по национальности она была
[music]
[музыка]
Russian German German so
русская немка немка так
correct The idea was
правильно Поня
wrong, she was for the
непра она была за
faith Yes, I can’t understand why Kadyrov is
веру Да я не могу понять почему Кадыров
Russian and Tsarina Katerina is not Russian Ruska ru
русский а царица Катерина не руска ру
herself VVA she wanted that’s what she wanted for herself
себя вва она хотела вот это она себе вс
[music] that’s exactly what
[музыка]
she learned  I
как раз вот этому всему училась она
just wanted to become Russian, which means it’s
просто желала стать русским значит это
not by birth
не по рождению
Russian by birth you can become a Slav
русс по кро ты можеь славянином стать
Slavyansk
Славянска
nationally I understand correctly that
национально я правильно понимаю что
Katerina she is like  Hitler
Катерина она она как Гитлер
was Russian, yes, that is, like Hitler, she
был рус да то есть Она как и Гитлер была
committed a crime, but she was
преступление совершала но она была
German, that is, not
немка то есть не
Russian, that is, she turns out, yes it
русская то есть она получается да
turns out, look that Hitler was in
получается смотрите что Гитлер был по
spirit in spirit, Russian in spirit, Russian in spirit And
духу по духу русская по духу русская А
I got it, I got it Cool, yeah Well, you can’t
понял понял Прикольно да Ну вам это не
understand that, of course  I understand, I understand, that is, and
понять конечно Понял понял то есть а
Kadyrov is talking about his nationality. I am
Кадыров он ружи что национальности Я
Ukrainian and Kadyrov is Russian or non-Russian
украинец а Кадыров русский или нерусский
by nationality. I told you
по национальности Я же тебе сказал украи
Ukraine is Ukrainian. Listen, who is Zelensky?
украинство Слушай а кто Зеленский по
nationality Jewish by nationality
национальности еврей по национальности
yes You sleep with only questions Let's talk about
да Спишь одними вопросами Давайте при
Jew and that a Jew by nationality he is
еврей и что еврей по национальности он
not Ukrainian is correct And that Yes he is not
не украинец правильно И что Да не
Ukrainian and he is not Ukrainian not but you and
украинец так и он не украинец не а вы а
you and you are fascists Yes you attacked a country
вы а вы фашисты Да вы напали на страну у
whose president is
которой президент
Jewish like Hitler you  you want the Jew
еврей как Гитлер вы вы хотите уть еврее
country mamo Yes look you you want you
страну мамо Да смотрите вы вы хотите вы
want
хотите
Zelensky the most influential Jew in
Зеленского самого влиятельного еврея
Ukraine Guy the Jews want you want him has
украи гаем евреи хотите хотите его уже
n’t been around for a long time I understand I understand  yes, well,
давно не было понял Понял да хорошо то
look, let's do it expressly Kadyrov
смотри давай так экспресс Кадыров
Kadyrov is Russian in spirit,
Кадыров по духу
let's listen, let's go To
русский давай слушай давай давай Чтоб
finish Kadyrov, Russian in spirit or
закончить Кадыров русский по духу или
not, let's ask those questions, let's
нет давай я те те вопрос давай я тебе
give you enough questions You haven't had enough questions for so long,
вопросов пода не хватит Ты уже сколько
look, I've been driving you so beautifully
нет смотри я тебя так погонял красиво
In short, let's finish
Короче давай завершим
this  already about Kadyrov, I told you everything,
эту уже про Кадырова я тебе всё сказал
you 10 times
ты 10 раз
Ira final Toro and asked the question. I said
Иру финальную Торо и зада вопро Я сказал
that you need to ask him.
что у него у него спросить надо у него А
Why don’t you  said Ask Katerina And
почему ты не сказал Спроси у Катерины А
his deputy said about Katerina
про катерину сказал у его заместителя с
Well, wait, you didn’t say Ask
Ну подожди ты же не сказал Спроси у
Katerina you said that you
Катерины ты сказал что ты
read you Read what she wrote
почитай ты Почитай что она писала про
about herself well Have you read that Kadyrov
себя хорошо А ты читал что Кадыров про
writes about himself You read that Kadyrov writes about himself
себя пишет Ты читал что Кадыров про себя
I haven’t read about Kadyrov, what am I
пишет а про Кадырова не читал да что
saying, I haven’t read it, I don’t understand I haven’t read it yet
говорю я не читал понял не читал пока
because he’s not yet such a
потому что это пока ещё не такой
historical character, it’s possible that
исторический персонаж станет исто можно
this will happen in the future, you know the 10 commandments Listen to
так насле вы 10 заповедей знаете Слушай
10  you know the commandments Listen, let me
10 заповедей знаете Слушай давай я тебе
ask you questions not You know, name the 10
вопросы зада не Ты знаешь вот назви 10
commandments and you will continue to ask me
заповедей и дальше будешь задавать мне
questions and well, name the 10 for no, I will not run away,
вопросы и ну назви 10 запо не не Убегу
name the 10 commandments I
назви 10 заповедей
will read the Lord your God
Зачитай я Господь Бог твой
wa for the second Do not make yourself an idol the third
ва за вторая Не делай себе кумира третья
do not
не
say the camera sri in  camera
произноси камеру сри в камеру
look at the camera look at the camera you
смотри в камеру смотри в камеру ты
read you look
читаешь ты глаза отводишь
at the camera look and speak at the piece of paper
в камеру смотри И говори ты на листок
Look, after every question,
Смотри после каждого вопро
I’m writing you a piece of paper, I’m writing so that
я листки тебе пишу пишу
I’m writing you a piece of paper, so that
чтобы я пишу тебе листки чтобы это чтобы
you’re there, I have an SS so no, so Name the 10
ты там у меня сси так нет так Назови 10
commandments without looking at the piece of paper where it
заповедей не погляда в листочек где он у
hangs,
тебя висит
come on, look at me like that and say the
давай смотри вот так на меня да и говори
10 commandments Come on, come on  Now I have a
10 заповедей Давай давай я теперь тебе
question for you No, you didn’t name it. I said,
вопрос Нет ты не назвал Я же сказал
name the 10 commandments and I’ll listen to you.
назовёшь 10 заповедей и я тебя выслушаю
You didn’t name the 10 commandments.
ты не назвал 10 заповедей
Yes, they are they.  they won’t
Да они те Они тебе не
help you Come on, you didn’t name the 10th station,
помогут Давай ты не назвал 10 заст
so don’t look further, just look Damn, you’re
так дальше не смотри ну смотришь Блин ты
looking at the piece of paper, damn it’s a shame, it’s just
смотришь на листочек блин позор просто
that an Orthodox Christian doesn’t know the
вот это православный не знает на память
10 commandments by heart, I have them here, I have them here,
10 заповедей у меня тут у меня тут
Okay, you’ll learn the 10 commandments Come,
ч Ладно выучишь 10 заповедей Приходи
let’s damn shorten the skills to Tey  Russia
давай блин скильки короче на Тей России
of all sorts of things, in short, it’s just a
всяких просто Короче просто
bummer, a post on my Instagram I don’t know
капец пидпись на мий инстагра Я не знаю
why this is for why there should be marvel
для чего це тоб для ч тоб там дивитись
at  otsey y face Ale for you tse one two
на оцей й фейс Але для тебе це один два
or three clicks Ale you trime me and I
або три клика Але ты тримае мене и я
will kti Wow in me there Kupa folov and in
буду кти Вау в мене там Купа фолов и в
me there will be a great mood to work robiti but
мене буде класний настрой щоб робити но
cool video write on my instr pok Andriy
крут вдео пись на мий instr пок Андрий
like
вот
this let me
так давай я тебя
check for you and
чекаю а